netatlantic.com 2013-08-16

# Privacy Policy | EU Safe Harbor | Net Atlantic

**High Email Deliverability**  
Your messages get through quickly and are seen by more of your audience.

**Powerful Email Tracking & Reporting**  
You know exactly how your messages perform. 

**Superior Segmentation and Automation**  
Choose who gets your emails and when.

**Personal & Expert Service**  
We try to answer every phone call and take care of your needs immediately.

#### Keep it Simple by Writing Content First

_by Cynthia_

Create your email marketing content once to make repeated mailings easier. This drives your email marketing effectiveness through the roof.

Read More Email Marketing Tips »

## Privacy Policy

Net Atlantic is committed to protecting the privacy of our web site visitors and clients. Your information will be held in the utmost care and confidence, and will not be used in any way that you have not consented to. We strive to uphold the highest industry standards in online privacy and permission marketing. For more information on how Net Atlantic enforces permission email marketing with our clients, please see our Anti-spam policy. 

Any personal information collected by Net Atlantic is used for the sole purpose of communicating with prospects, customers, and contacts that have requested to receive information from us regarding specific marketing events, materials, or other information specifically advertised by Net Atlantic in promotional material. Personal information will be held confidential and will never be used, sold, loaned, rented, or otherwise distributed or disclosed to any third party for any reason. 

Employees and personnel of Net Atlantic who have access to personally identifiable information of customers, including financial data, such as credit card number or social security number, are required to keep the information strictly confidential and are not permitted to use this information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for Net Atlantic on behalf of the customer.

Net Atlantic is subject to the jurisdiction of the United States Federal Trade Commission, and we adhere to all EU Safe Harbor Principles.

© 1995-2013 Net Atlantic, Inc. All rights reserved. 

We are not a mailing list broker and do not sell or rent email lists.
